festicket.com 2015-06-11

# Privacy Policy and Information About Cookies – Festicket

This policy (together with our Terms Of Use policy) sets out the basis on which any personal data we collect from you, or that you provide to us, will be processed by us. Please read the following carefully to understand our views and practices regarding your personal data and how we will treat it.

For the purpose of the Data Protection Act 1998 (the “Act”), the data controller is YESLAB Limited, company number 07923345 trading as Festicket.com of Innovation Warehouse 1, East Poultry Avenue, London, EC1A 9PT (“Festicket.com”). 

## INFORMATION WE MAY COLLECT FROM YOU

We may collect and process the following data about you:

Information that you provide by filling in forms on our site www.festicket.com (our site). This includes information provided at the time of registering to use our site, subscribing to our service, posting reviews or other material on our site or requesting further services. We may also ask you for information when you enter a competition or promotion sponsored by Festicket.com and when you report a problem with our site.

If you contact us, we may keep a record of that correspondence.

We may also ask you to complete surveys that we use for research purposes, although you do not have to respond to them.

Details of purchases of festival packages or festival tickets that you carry out through our site and of the fulfilment of your bookings.

Details of your visits to our site including, but not limited to, traffic data, location data, logs and other communication data, whether this is required for our own billing purposes or otherwise and the resources that you access. 

## IP ADDRESSES

We may collect information about your computer, including where available your IP address, operating system and browser type, for system administration and to report aggregate information to our advertisers. This is statistical data about our users' browsing actions and patterns, and does not identify any individual.

## COOKIES

Our website uses cookies to distinguish you from other users of our website. This helps us to provide you with a good experience when you browse our website and also allows us to improve our site.

A cookie is a small file of letters and numbers that we store on your browser or the hard drive of your computer if you agree. Cookies contain information that is transferred to your computer's hard drive.

Some cookies that we use are essential to process your booking such as allowing our site to remember the details of your festival booking when you proceed to check-out and pay. 

Other cookies that we use enable us to recognise you when you return to our site estimate our audience size and usage pattern, store information about your preferences, and so allow us to customise our site and to provide you with offers that are targeted at your individual interests, speed up your searches and allow you to use our site in a way that makes your browsing experience more convenient. If you register with us or complete our online forms, we will use cookies to remember your details during your current visit, and any future visits provided the cookie was not deleted in the interim.

We, Google and other third parties set cookies (either which are set by us or the third party provider) in order to track your internet behaviour after you leave the Festicket.com website in order to display to you advertisements that may be of interest to you when you browse third party websites – commonly known as “behavioural advertising”. If you do not want us to carry out any behavioural advertising, you will need to opt out of all of the following: Google Analytics display advertising, and DoubleClick, both of which you can opt out of on the Google website using this link: Settings for Google Ads; and Dynamic Ad Serving which uses the Teracent cookie, which you can opt-out of [here](http://www.teracent.com/about-us/opt-out). You can also customise your preferences for display advertising using these links and can choose to opt out of some but not all display advertising according to your preference. 

We will ask you for your consent to our use of cookies in accordance with this policy when you visit our site. If you do not consent, but then continue to view our site or make a booking on our site, you will be deemed to have consented to us setting cookies in accordance with this policy. 

You can block cookies by activating the setting on your browser that allows you to refuse the setting of all or some cookies. To find out more about cookies, including how to see that cookies have been set and how to manage and delete them, visit [www.allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/). However, if you use your browser settings to block all cookies (including essential cookies) you may not be able to access all or parts of our site. Unless you have adjusted your browser setting so that it will refuse cookies, our system will issue cookies as soon you visit our site.

## WHERE WE STORE YOUR PERSONAL DATA

The data that we collect from you may be transferred to, and stored at, a destination outside the European Economic Area ("EEA"). It may also be processed by staff operating outside the EEA who work for us or for one of our suppliers. Such staff maybe engaged in, among other things, the fulfilment of your bookings, the processing of your payment details and the provision of support services. By submitting your personal data, you agree to this transfer, storing or processing. We will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this privacy policy.

All information you provide to us is stored on our secure servers. Any payment transactions will be encrypted. Where we have given you (or where you have chosen) a password that enables you to access certain parts of our site, you are responsible for keeping this password confidential. We ask you not to share a password with anyone.

Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure. Although we will do our best to protect your personal data, we cannot guarantee the security of your data transmitted to our site; any transmission is at your own risk. Once we have received your information, we will use strict procedures and security features to try to prevent unauthorised access.

## USES MADE OF THE INFORMATION

We use information held about you in the following ways:

To ensure that content from our site is presented in the most effective manner for you and for your computer. 

To provide you with information, products or services that you request from us or which we feel may interest you, where you have consented to be contacted for such purposes. 

To carry out our obligations arising from any contracts for festivals or festival packages entered into between you and us.

To allow you to participate in interactive features of our products and services, when you choose to do so.

To notify you about changes to our products or services.

To display advertising to you that may be of interest when you browse other sites (see the section on “Cookies” above).

We may also use your data to provide you with information about goods and services which may be of interest to you and we may contact you about these by post or telephone. 

If you are an existing customer, we will only contact you by electronic means (e-mail or SMS) with information about products and services similar to those that were the subject of a previous sale to you. If you are a new customer, we will only contact you by electronic means if you have consented to this. 

We will not pass your personal data to third parties without your prior consent.

If you do not want us to use your data in this way, please either tick the relevant box situated on the form on which we collect your data, unsubscribe to any emails your receive or notify us at [contact@festicket.com](mailto:contact@festicket.com).

## DISCLOSURE OF YOUR INFORMATION

We may disclose your personal information to third parties:

In the event that we sell or buy any business or assets, in which case we may disclose your personal data to the prospective seller or buyer of such business or assets.

If we or substantially all of our assets are acquired by a third party, in which case personal data held by us about our customers will be one of the transferred assets.

If we are under a duty to disclose or share your personal data in order to comply with any legal obligation, or in order to enforce or apply our terms of use or our booking conditions or to protect the rights, property, or safety of Festicket.com, our customers, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organisations for the purposes of fraud protection and credit risk reduction.

## ACCESS TO INFORMATION

The Act gives you the right to access information held about you. Your right of access can be exercised in accordance with the Act. Any access request may be subject to a fee of £10 to meet our costs in providing you with details of the information we hold about you.

## CHANGES TO OUR PRIVACY POLICY

Any changes we may make to our privacy policy in the future will be posted on this page and, where appropriate, notified to you by e-mail.

## CONTACT

Any questions regarding this privacy policy should be addressed to [contact@festicket.com](mailto:contact@festicket.com).
